kimovil.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Terms :: Kimovil.com

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of the Terms of Use of the website.

In compliance with the provisions of Organic Law 15/1999 of December 13, Protection of Personal Data, KIMOVIL SMARTPHONE COMPARISON S.L. (Kimovil.com) reports that it:

  1. Kimovil.com not collect user data.

  2. Where requested, and the user provides an email address, mobile phone or other electronic means, the user expressly agrees and authorizes that these media are used preferably as a communication channel, such as channel to comply with all or any of the purposes above informed and channel through which to inform you of any other relevant changes that occur in the Portal.

  3. Data Sharing: At times, we may share anonymous information relating to Users of the Site (eg, behavior patterns, purchase options, traffic volumes or other information), but such data or information no case contain personal information that could identify the Users;

  * (A) A police, administrative, judicial or other similar bodies in legally required cases, subject to receiving the mandatory injunction and, in particular, when the investigation of any suspected criminal offense occurs or exists Violations of the Terms of Use;

  * (B) In the event of a corporate transaction of purchase and / or sale of an area of ​​business or assets you may have, in such a case may share personal data with the prospective seller or buyer of such business area or active.

  * (C) A business engaged in the provision of the Services offered through the Site, in order to know their potential customers.

  1. Kimovil.com makes use of cookies, either through their own means or through third party contracted to provide measurement services in relation to the users browsing the site. 

Cookies are files sent to the browser by a web server in order to record the activities of users during its navigation. Cookies allow us to measure the audience and traffic parameters and number of entries, and the most significant transactions of users.

Users have the ability to configure your browser to be notified of the receipt of cookies and to prevent their installation on your browser. Please read the instructions and manuals on your browser for more information.

Cookies are used in the Portal:

  * A) Session cookie, which has a temporary basis for the sole purpose of enabling certain features of the Portal and Effective subsequent browsing; 
  * B) Cookie navigation, which is reset each time the user enters from an external URL; 
  * C) User Cookie, which is used to better understand how the Portal users and to offer users greater ease and speed of access to the Website and display your information interact; 
  * D) Third Party Cookies (Mixpanel, GoSquared, Google adwords / analytics, CAM, Visitor ID and Addthis) which are used for the production of statistics and keep track of the navigation of users in the Portal. 

Also authorize affiliates and certain third set and access cookies on the computers of the users of the portal. Some of these third parties may collect and use information about users' visits to the Website and other web portals offer content that may be of interest to the User. The use of these third party cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not the privacy policy Kimovil.com.

  1. The Users guarantee that your personal data provided are true, accurate, complete and current, and that Users are solely responsible for any damage or harm, direct or indirect, that may arise as a result of a breach of such obligation. In the event that the information provided by a User belong to someone other than who provides the data, the user must inform the third party of the contents in this Privacy Policy, and to make them available, the User acknowledges and states that he obtained the permission of the third party to provide their data to Kimovil.com. 

Also, for the purposes of the duty to ensure quality and updating of data, the User shall inform Kimovil.com any changes that may occur in the data.

  1. In response to his concern to ensure the security and confidentiality of your data, we inform you that Kimovil.com have adopted the levels of security required for the protection of personal data and technical means have been installed at its disposal to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of personal data provided through the Portal access.

  2. The User has the right to access, rectification, cancellation and opposition (ARCO), which can be exercised by postal communication, and photocopy of ID, with the subject "ref LOPD" to email bajas@kimovil.com
